<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="bookstore.xslt"?>
<books>
  <book category="cookbook">
    <title lang="en">The Joy of Cooking</title>
    <author>Irma S. Rombauer</author>
    <year>1997</year>
    <price>€20.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>Learn the joys of cooking from one of the most pleasant foodie writers around!</description>
  </book>
  <book category="cookbook">
    <title lang="en">The New Best Recipe</title>
    <author>Cook's Illustrated Magazine</author>
    <year>2004</year>
    <price>€25.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>Learn the latest recipes from the masters of honest food.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="cookbook">  
    <title lang="en">Mastering the Art of French Cooking</title>
    <author>Julia Childe</author>
    <year>2001</year>
    <price>€25.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>Julia Chide teaches you about more than just escargot and frog legs, its time to educate yourself!</description>
  </book>
  <book category="cookbook">  
    <title lang="en">Betty Crocker's Cookbook</title>
    <author>Betty Crocker</author>
    <year>1981</year>
    <price>€16.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>A classic that defined the modern cookbook.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="cookbook">  
    <title lang="en">Vegetarian Cooking for Everyone</title>
    <author>Deborah Madison</author>
    <year>2007</year>
    <price>€15.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>Impress your friends and be mor politically correct alearn how to please those veggie eaters at the dinner party.</description>
  </book>
  
  
  <book category="Action">  
    <title lang="en">The Hunger Games Collection</title>
    <author>Suzanne Collins</author>
    <year>2008</year>
    <price>€20.00</price>
    <ageRating>Young Adults</ageRating>
    <description>Katniss Everdee has just volunteered for tribute, the beginning of a battle royale to the death... Let the games begin.</description>
  </book>
 <book category="Action">  
    <title lang="en">The Da Vinci Code</title>
    <author>Dan Brown</author>
    <year>2006</year>
    <price>€12.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>A modern favourite, with suspenseful action throughout, its a well-known page turner. Can you unravel the code before you turn the last page? </description>
  </book>
  <book category="Action">  
    <title lang="en">Stormbreaker</title>
    <author>Dan Brown</author>
    <year>2004</year>
    <price>€10.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young Adults</ageRating>
    <description>Alex Rider is a teenage spy, and he's fun to read about, this is one for all those young James Bond enthusiasts!</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Action">  
    <title lang="en">Killing Floor</title>
    <author>Lee Child</author>
    <year>2006</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description> The debut of writer Lee child. Tough ex-cop Reachers first outing in the action crime world, soon to be a major live-action film.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Action">  
    <title lang="en">Jurassic Park</title>
    <author>Michael Crichton</author>
    <year>1993</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>This many need no introductions but don't be misled by the films who have stolen the spotlight, you may be surprised by how well thought the writing is in the original journey to Isla Sorna's Jurassic Park. </description>
  </book>
  
  
  
  <book category="Fantasy">  
    <title lang="en">A Game of Thrones</title>
    <author>George R.R. Martin</author>
    <year>1996</year>
    <price>€12.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>Cloak and dagger intrigue is bountiful, with rich characterisations and lore to satisfy even the most avid reader of fantasy. Just remember, when you play the game of thrones, you play to win!</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Fantasy">  
    <title lang="en">The Lord of the Rings</title>
    <author>J.R.R. Tolkien</author>
    <year>1973</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>Born in the mind of one of the greatest writers and crafter of worlds; the world of middle-earth as it was written by the master himself, a series of books which truly gave definition to the genre. Before the end a fellowship will be formed and broken, battles will be won and lost... this is the war of the ring as it was told almost 50 years ago.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Fantasy">  
    <title lang="en">Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone</title>
    <author>J.K. Rowling</author>
    <year>1997</year>
    <price>€9.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>The original hit which grew to be one of the most popular books of all time. Harry isn't just a boy with a scar on his head... he's a wizard!</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Fantasy">  
    <title lang="en">Eragon</title>
    <author>J.R.R. Tolkien</author>
    <year>2005</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young Adults</ageRating>
    <description>A young man finds a shiny stone in a forbidden mountain range... The start to an epic tale of high-fantasy, akin to Star Wars in scope!</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Fantasy">  
    <title lang="en">His Dark Materials</title>
    <author>Phillip Pullman</author>
    <year>1997</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Everyone</ageRating>
    <description>A series set in one of the most vivid worlds created for young people. An emotionally rich tale that is surprising thought-provoking, with one of the most satisfying endings this reader has ever had the pleasure of digesting.</description>
  </book>
  
  
  
  <book category="Science-Fiction">  
    <title lang="en">1984</title>
    <author>George Orwell</author>
    <year>1949</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>1984 already came and went, but in this near-prophetic vision of the future from 1949 still holds up as one great dystopian futures. Undeniably original and hauntingly close to reality.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Science-Fiction">  
    <title lang="en">Dune</title>
    <author>Frank Herbert</author>
    <year>1965</year>
    <price>€12.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young adults</ageRating>
    <description>Set in the far future amidst a feudal empire in the stars, planetary dynasties are controlled by noble houses who in turn owe allegience to the Imperial house Corrino. It centers on a desert planet known as Arrakis, a near uninhabitable desert planet which is the sole source of "spice". The most valuable resource in the universe as it is essential for space travel. The story is complex and explores multii-layered interactions of politics, religion, ecology, technology and human emotion as the forces of the empire conspire for control of arrakis. Think Game of Thrones on a grander scale... In space! </description>
  </book>
  <book category="Science-Fiction">  
    <title lang="en">Foundation</title>
    <author>Isaac Asimov</author>
    <year>1951</year>
    <price>€12.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young adults</ageRating>
    <description>Set amidst a 12'000 year old empire which has begun to stagnate and die. Only Hari Seldon the creator of a revolutionary science he calls psychohistory, can see this future. The ignorant empire will succumb to barbarism and warfare for 30'000 years, he cannot stop this. To preserve knowledge and the last hope for mankind, he gathers the greatest minds of the greatest society, scientists, artists and scholars, and places them on foundation, a sanctuary and a beacon of hope which must survive 30'000 years of turmoil using only his interpretations of humanities pschological history, to map the future. Fantastic science-fiction from page one.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Science-Fiction">  
    <title lang="en">Frankenstein</title>
    <author>Mary Shelley</author>
    <year>1818</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>A book that needs no introduction, written by Mary Shelley at a time when only men were considered capable writers. It is considered by many to be the "first" science-fiction book ever written. Simply put a mans obsession leads him to create a living man from multiple dead ones, tragedy ensues when he rejects his creation. At once a thriller, romance and a cautionary tale about the danger that science poses without consideration of the consequences or purpose it will have. This is well before the nuclear bombm, which is when that debate was truly taken seriously, making this far ahead of its time.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Science-Fiction">  
    <title lang="en">Shades Children</title>
    <author>Garth Nix</author>
    <year>1997</year>
    <price>€10.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young adults</ageRating>
    <description>Set in a ghostly urban wasteland, the remainder of humanity is made up of children after a mysterious event left cold overlords in control of earth and its resources, that includes people.Their rules are simple, the children remain imprisoned unitil the age of 14 when they are harvested to create new biomechanical monstrosities of different forms. The children are bred differently depending on their purpose. Some are kept alive to breed, some are fed high-protein diets and steroids while being forced to exercise... but all are seen as resources. The mysteriious shade, who was once a man and is now a machine, guides the surviving escapees... but is he any better than the overlords? Pretty fantastic premise for a dystopian adventure if you ask us!</description>
  </book>
  
  
  <book category="Graphic Novels">  
    <title lang="en">Watchmen</title>
    <author>Alan Moore</author>
    <year>1987</year>
    <price>€18.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>One of the most influential graphic novels of all-time. Consider that it has been studied in college campuses. It chronicles the fall from glory of a superhero group, it dissects the heroes and the genre tropes as they are hunted by an unknown assassin.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Graphic Novels">  
    <title lang="en">V for Vendetta</title>
    <author>Alan Moore</author>
    <year>1982</year>
    <price>€18.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young adults</ageRating>
    <description>"Remember, remember the fifth of November" A terrifying tale of the loss of freedom in a totalitarian world very similar to Orwells "1984" and almost as prophetic of our present-day. Set in a future UK which has given itself over to fascism, a figure masked in the guise of Guy Fawkes battles to stir rebellion against the totalitarian government. Deep characterisations and versimilitude crafted with a clarity and intelligience that Moore has made his own.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Graphic Novels">  
    <title lang="en">Batman: Arkham Asylum - A Serious House on Serious Earth</title>
    <author>Grant Morrison</author>
    <year>1989</year>
    <price>€18.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>Painted with a haunting beauty, the inmates of arkham have escaped and taken control of the asylum on April Fools day. They demans Batman in exchange for hostages, and he accepts the challenge. His physical and mental endurance are stretched to their limits in the villain gauntlet and his own sanity must come into question.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Graphic Novels">  
    <title lang="en">Maus</title>
    <author>Alan Moore</author>
    <year>1986</year>
    <price>€25.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young adults</ageRating>
    <description>A contemporary classic, the story of Vladek Spiegelman and his wife, surviving in Nazi occuppied Europe. The author portrays the turmoil in comic format, brilliantly capturing the reality of war for those pursued, exploring the themes of guilt, relief and survival, while also depicting the affects of survival on the children of survivors. A must-read with striking imagery.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Graphic Novels">  
    <title lang="en">Walking Dead</title>
    <author>Robert Kirkman</author>
    <year>2003</year>
    <price>€16.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young adults</ageRating>
    <description>The graphic novel that laid the groundwork for the popular series of the same name. Taking the zombie genre and building a character driven story about people, the consequences of actions and responsibility. Follow Rick as he searches for his family and a place to start a new life in a harsh and unforgiving apocalypse, where government and order has crumbled... also zombies want to eat everyones brains!</description>
  </book>
  

  
  <book category="Mystery/Thriller">  
    <title lang="en">The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo</title>
    <author>Stieg Larsson</author>
    <year>2005</year>
    <price>€14.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>First in a series of gripping myssteries in the "Millenium" series.  When a veteran reporter takes on a job for an aging corporate magnate, he must enlist the help of a young hacker girl with poor social skills and a photographic memory must work together to solve a 50 year old murder case... a case which seems to have a conspiratorial origin.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Mystery/Thriller">  
    <title lang="en">The Hound of the Baskervilles</title>
    <author>Sir Arthur Conan Doyle</author>
    <year>1902</year>
    <price>€8.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young Adults</ageRating>
    <description>The third in the classic series narrating the adventures of detective Sherlock Holmes and his stalworth companion Dr.Watson. It details a mysterious case of a murdered countryside noble at the hands of a ghostly apparition of a diabolical hound, things are clearly not as they seem... </description>
  </book>
  <book category="Mystery/Thriller">  
    <title lang="en">Cross Justice</title>
    <author>James Patterson</author>
    <year>2003</year>
    <price>€10.99</price>
    <ageRating>Mature</ageRating>
    <description>The chronological first in the detective Alex Cross series. Returning to his North Coralina hometown after his cousin is accused of a horrendous crime, he attempts to find proof of innocence. What he unearths is a family secret that challenges everything he's ever known.</description>
  </book>
  <book category="Mystery/Thriller">  
    <title lang="en">Shutter Island</title>
    <author>Dennis Lehane</author>
    <year>2003</year>
    <price>€12.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young Adults</ageRating>
    <description>A psychological thriller/mystery set in 1954. U.S Marshal Teddy Daniels, ex-war veteran and his new partner Chuck, investigate a Shutter Islands Ashcliffe Hospital for the criminally insane. As a hurricane hits the island, hints of radical experimentation and surgeries arise and the marshal must question even his own sanity as things unravel. Now a major live-action film. </description>
  </book>  
  <book category="Mystery/Thriller">  
    <title lang="en">And Then There Were None</title>
    <author>Agatha Christie</author>
    <year>2004</year>
    <price>€12.99</price>
    <ageRating>Young Adults</ageRating>
    <description>First there were ten - a variey of strangers are summoned to island by an eccentric millionaire, when they arrive he is nowhere to be found and they soon realise that they all share a secret that has darkened theor lives, a hidden past of sor which they are unwilling to reveal. All have been marked for death. </description>
  </book>  

  
  <suggestions>
    <title>My name is Mark</title>
    <author>Mark McDonald</author>
  </suggestions>
<suggestions><title>my name is mark</title><author>Mark Mc Donald</author></suggestions><suggestions><title>cookbook</title><author>john</author></suggestions><suggestions><title>john</title><author>luke</author></suggestions><suggestions><title>t</title><author>t</author></suggestions><suggestions><title>sandman slim</title><author>luke carroll</author></suggestions><suggestions><title>Stormbreaker</title><author>Dan Brown</author></suggestions></books>
